yes guys so recently I flew over 10,000
kilometers halfway across the Earth to
Asia specifically barley Indonesia to
play some Futures tournaments four weeks
of events where I'm going to be
competing in singles and doubles and
today I'm going to be showing you my
first training day here in barley to
make sure that I'm preparing my body in
the best way for week number one I'm
going to be taking through my tennis
sessions my gym sessions what I'm eating
what I'm getting up to and stay tuned to
the end of the video to see what the
actual tournament site looks like
because it's crazy yes guys we've just
woken up we're heading down to breakfast
now yeah very nice weather 25°
relatively humid I'm looking forward to
this breakfast cuz I've heard some great
[Music]
things this place is insane so much
choice I went with just some eggs bread
avocado it was unbelievable taste test
of
this that's actually so good
this is so
good and then it was all about getting
prepared for the first tennis session of
the
day good start to the filming session
lifts broke so we've now got to track up
15 floors of stairs here we
go at least we'll be
ready yeah guys so we've just got to the
tennis court
looking very nice you've got some pretty
cool Shrubbery in the background there's
Rory playing with a tennis ball like a
dog here to film some content uh we got
the call for two and a bit hours so
going to film a cool video and then me
and Jamie going to practice for about an
hour and a bit and then uh yeah head to
the club later
on let's go really trying to feel the
ball here on the first Training Day not
really trying to think too much about
how I'm playing or where the balls going
and let me tell you these conditions
were tough yes guys so as you can tell
we're sweating a lot out here so you got
to stay hydrated so I've got with me
kind of for this trip basically a
massive pack of like these electrolytes
I got with me I'm going to take one to
two per day I've Al also got these
electrolyte fast chews I'm going to try
it now lemon flavor supposed to
just chewable tablet pretty good and
then yeah lots of
water Jamie is struggling a little bit
with his GR
so humid out here my grip is completely
just wet so it's really hard to grip
it only going to go like 60 70% there
just want to build it back in these
conditions
yes guys practice one finished good
practice about an hour and 15 hour and
20 minutes don't want to go too crazy
sweating so
much there you go just shows you how
much we're sweating going to do a little
bit of a cool down head to the gym lift
a little bit of weight today is Saturday
so I've got until Monday to prepare so
I've got two days so I usually don't
like to lift the day before but I'll
lift today just a kind of a full body
make sure the body's working moving
nicely and then we'll head to the club
later and uh yeah try and secure some
practice some stringing and some
practice balls you obviously appreciate
every single one of you guys that
watches and likes and subscribes it
allows these trips to be possible Chase
my dreams and uh yeah going to take you
guys along with me post training I
headed to the gym to do a circuit
consisting of upper and lower body a
little bit of a circuit I'm obviously
not playing for the next few days so I
like to get a LIF
[Music]
in through the CH
deep on the wings
in
the I also work kind of plyometric
movements after doing the squat just cuz
I don't like to do too much heavy leg
work before tournaments and just feel
nice and springy and plyometric for the
matches
for
thein and of course finished with the
cool down on the bike and a trip to the
[Music]
[Applause]
sauna oh yeah little bit of SAA recovery
nice big saer to myself I usually do
about 5 10 minutes in here and then uh
yeah follow it up with uh a nice cold
shower and then I think we'll head to
lunch I usually do a little bit of
stretching in here just to help with the
the Muscle Recovery um I think saers are
really beneficial if you can go three
four times consistently each week I'm a
real big believer in saers so yeah for
all of you guys that are considering
going in Spar and stuff like that in
saers I'd highly recommend it also
recommend the ice plunge but I don't
know whether they have one here but it's
basically just really cold water like an
ice bath not very fun but has to be done
for Recovery they don't have hot water
so I'm I have to have ice C
[Music]
shower well that explains it should have
showered in the room big mistake
[Music]
got myself an iced
Americano The Barley stand is pretty
expensive this and this sparkling water
cost me
£7 which quite a lot actually so yeah
they didn't have prices but I needed a
caffeine hit uh with us going to the
practice TI in uh just a bit Jamie's
preparing he's hoping he's going to get
in he's I think he's alternate 18 or
something so we're both praying Rory me
and him are all praying that he gets in
and I'm slightly optimistic
so it's one good iced Americano I can't
lie got some chicken apple some
rice what are your thoughts pretty good
rating out of
10 7.1
7.1 some interesting flavors I can't
lie needs a bit of sauce though I'll
give it a
6.2 not the best wouldn't order again
but it gets the job done then it was
time to head to the tennis club and the
tennis venue to see what the courts were
like and when we got there we were a
little bit shocked right guys we've uh
assess the courts this is where we're
playing
what do we think good
level it's not looking good boys but in
reality they had literally just built
seven brand new courts I think literally
the week before these courts looked in
amazing condition so yeah the site looks
insane they've got barley on the back of
the Court which is epic we can film
really easily because they've actually
got the back of the the fencing is not
on so yeah it looks sick I'm really
looking forward to it now and they even
had a tennis players area I was
completely in shock so this is for the
players it's completely air conditioned
so it's actually freezing cold they got
like a blower uh air conditioning unit
over there it's really nice yeah very
solid site I'm I'm going to go to the
tourn Des now see if I can get some
racket strong overall I'm very impressed
this site looks epic at the time of
recording I've also played my first
matches and I can tell you that for
first round of qualies they have umpires
Bull Boys everything so make sure that
you go over to my main Channel And
subscribe because when the video is
released from this first trip it's going
to be awesome